<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Know Me</string>

    <string name="start_button">Start from here</string>
    <string name="start_content">Monica Ma\nDigital Resume</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">Monica Ma</string>
    <string name="title_skill">skills</string>
    <string name="skills">• <b><i>Programming Languages:</i></b> \nJava, Python, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, iOS Swift, Kotlin, C++, SQL\n
            \n• <b><i>Professional Skills:</i></b> \nGit/GitHub, Unix, Maven, Gradle, MongoDB, MySQL, JMeter, JUnit, JSON, Tomcat,
            jQuery, Bootstrap, D3.js, Google Map API, Amazon EC2, R, Tableau\n
            \n• <b><i>Courses:</i></b> \nData Structures and Algorithms, Algorithms and Computational Complexity, Database Systems,
Web Development, Android Development, iOS Mobile Development, Machine Learning, Data Science</string>
    <string name="title_education">Education</string>
    <string name="education">• <b><i>University of Washington, Seattle, WA</i></b>
            \nM.S. in Management Information Systems, Information School
            \nSpecialization in Software Development, GPA: 3.89/4.0\n
            \n• <b><i>Shanghai Jiao Tong University, Shanghai</i></b>
            \nB.S. M.S. in Bioinformatics and Pharmaceutical Science, GPA: 3.95/4.0, Rank: 1/76</string>
    <string name="title_work">Work Experience</string>
    <string name="work"><b><i>Software Engineer (Full-time Internship)\nAgilysys, Inc., Bellevue, WA</i></b>
        \n• Worked on Agilysys Buy team in Java backend development with Spring framework for a point-of-sale kiosk used in 1/3 of corporate cafeteria nationwide
        \n• Designed and implemented RESTful APIs for the partnership with Microsoft to allow customers to search
        stores, get items and update payment, etc.
        \n• Built MongoDB template to capture the item data with the Spring MongoDB
        \n• Wrote unit tests (Mockito and TestNG) and test suites, tested HTTP requests and responses by JMeter\n
        \n<b><i>Associate Specialist in Digital Solution\nMedtronic Inc., Shanghai</i></b>
        \n• Analyzed over 2,000 Parkinson patients’ data using Python, used Tableau to create multi-metrics dashboards, driving business decisions on patients’ media preferences
        \n• Built new features within Medtronic’s official website and WeChat platforms resulting in 233% increase in the number of users, managed the development and testing of patient stories/videos’ web apps</string>
    <string name="title_activity_second">More...</string>
</resources>
